
[
  {
    "question": "One's family and relations ",
    "choice1": "kin",
    "choice2": "prodigy",
    "choice3": "acquaintance",
    "choice4": "copacetic",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "a young person who is unusually talented in some way",
   "choice1": "kin",
    "choice2": "prodigy",
    "choice3": "acquaintance",
    "choice4": "copacetic",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "a person one knows slightly, but who is not a close friend",
    "choice1": "kin",
    "choice2": "prodigy",
    "choice3": "acquaintance",
    "choice4": "copacetic",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "to think about something carefully ",
    "choice1": "musings",
    "choice2": "insinuating",
    "choice3": "ornery",
    "choice4": "kin",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "to say (something, especially something bad or insulting) in an indirect way",
   "choice1": "musings",
    "choice2": "insinuating",
    "choice3": "ornery",
    "choice4": "copacetic",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "easily annoyed or angered; difficult to deal with",
    "choice1": "musings",
    "choice2": "insinuating",
    "choice3": "ornery",
    "choice4": "prodigy",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "in excellent order",
    "choice1": "kin",
    "choice2": "prodigy",
    "choice3": "acquaintance",
    "choice4": "copacetic",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "a child who causes trouble usually in a playful way",
    "choice1": "scamp",
    "choice2": "contaminated",
    "choice3": "compromise",
    "choice4": "rummaging",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "to make (something) dangerous, dirty, or impure by adding something harmful or undesirable to it.",
    "choice1": "scamp",
    "choice2": "contaminated",
    "choice3": "compromise",
    "choice4": "rummaging",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "a way of reaching an agreement in which each person or group gives up something that was wanted in order to end an argument",
   "choice1": "scamp",
    "choice2": "contaminated",
    "choice3": "compromise",
    "choice4": "rummaging",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "make a thorough search to find something",
   "choice1": "scamp",
    "choice2": "contaminated",
    "choice3": "compromise",
    "choice4": "rummaging",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "a negative feeling or problem that becomes worse",
    "choice1": "festering",
    "choice2": "meddling",
    "choice3": "bawling",
    "choice4": "snooping",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "interfere with something that is not your business",
    "choice1": "festering",
    "choice2": "meddling",
    "choice3": "bawling",
    "choice4": "snooping",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "to cry very loudly",
   "choice1": "festering",
    "choice2": "meddling",
    "choice3": "bawling",
    "choice4": "snooping",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "to look for private information about someone or something",
   "choice1": "festering",
    "choice2": "meddling",
    "choice3": "bawling",
    "choice4": "snooping",
    "answer": 4
  }
  
]
  
